Speed, spirit,
and a really large fish,
the three tools of a hero!
Hang on. That doesn't make any...
Speed, spirit and a very large...?
I'm getting ahead of myself.
If I'm gonna tell this story...
I've got to catch you up on everything.
So, there was
this town once, Baltese.
Oh, you should have seen it.
Which I guess you are now, so, good.
The sort of place
where everything felt possible
or even magical,
like that lady
making the fountain go nuts.
Check this out!
Or these kids,
doing some sophisticated, magical...
Inappropriate!
Anyway,
times changed, like times do.
And let me tell you, it wasn't good.
There was the Great Foreign War,
and after that,
people in Baltese just stopped believing.
Nothing felt possible or magical,
and then the clouds rolled in.
Strange clouds that never break
or budge or snow.
The town's been stuck,
but things are about to get unstuck.
I mean, otherwise, why would I tell
this story? That'd be pretty boring.
Peter is an orphan
being raised by an old soldier.
The soldier knows about fighting
and hardship and danger,
so he's training the boy
for that kind of life.
But the boy knows there must be more.
Peter, other children have families,
but as orphan, you have a rare privilege.
You can devote yourself to soldier's life.
Attention.
Here is coin for today.
Get our fish and bread now
before you begin your marching.
Older bread the better,
bread to make your teeth... strong,
and small fish
so you are accustomed to hunger.
- For what are we?
- We're soldiers, sir.
- And what is this?
- The world.
And what is the world?
Hard.
- Good morning, Mrs. Taylor.
- Good morning, Peter.
Hmm.
Are you going to the opera tonight, madam?
Certainly. The only thing
I enjoy in this town.
Good morning.
Ah, Peter, I saved you
a beautiful piece today
that you can't refuse.
Come on, you know Vilna.
I know. I know.
Old bread and small fish.
Careful!
No!
Hey, Peter. Here's
the most disappointing fish for you.
Oh no, no, no, no!
Mind yourself.
What?
"The most profound and difficult questions
that could possibly be posed
by the human heart or mind
will be answered
for the price of one coin."
One coin.
I have to know.
Whoa.
Your Guardian Vilna Lutz will be angry
if you return without dinner.
Where'd you come from?
How do you know that?
But you must ask yourself,
one day without food
or the rest of your life without knowing?
Mm.
She lives.
What?
- How do you...?
- One coin, one question.
Careful.
Well, my family died in the war when I was
three years old. There was a battle...
There was a battle.
Vilna Lutz rescued you,
and he's raising you to be a soldier.
- What?
- I know.
When my father died, my mother...
She was expecting a child. I also know.
Sergeant Lutz told me
that during the birth,
both she and the baby died, but...
But you remember?
I held her. I know I did.
Your sister?
My sister.
She was so small and she was...
Alive. Yes.
- Why did Vilna Lutz tell me...?
- No.
You will only get one question,
so be careful.
Will I ever see her...?
Stop! Stop and think for a moment.
Think of the right question, Peter.
How do I find her?
Yes, good. Very good.
And the answer is...
follow the elephant.
- You're having fun with me.
- You have your answer.
"Follow the elephant?"
I gave you our one coin for today.
You made a choice. You asked a question.
And you cheated me.
Follow the elephant and you'll find her.
But there aren't any elephants here!
Just as you say.
We have no dinner tonight
because of Fortune Teller?
Yes, sir, but she knew
so much about me! About you! I...
How could she know about me?
I do not even know about me.
She said that my sister lives
and to follow an elephant.
An elephant? Your sister?
I know, sir. You've told me
all these years that my sister...
Not again with this.
Your poor mother, your sister.
Both of them died.
I saved you,
which was all that I could do!
But I...
Top shelf.
Kitchen cabinet.
A storybook? Who is Romain De Smedt...?
Gimme, gimme, gimme!
Romain De Smedt drive me crazy.
Young soldier I served with, good boy.
But he read this book at night
which remind him of home,
of mother, of comfort.
I had to cure him of all of this.
So I stole De Smedt's book.
What?
And it worked.
Without this book, he turned
into the most fearsome soldier in army.
Why are you telling me this?
Where there is comfort,
there is innocence.
Where there is innocence,
there can never be soldier.
Peter, today,
you were told... a fairy tale.
One just as false as any in this book!
There are no elephants.
If there were elephants...
...I would spot them immediately!
Ah. You hear that?
Some kind of disturbance.
Hand me the spyglass.
It's just the cats.
Spyglass. Spyglass, Peter.
Spyglass! Spyglass! Peter!
Amazing.
Very clever.
Yeah. That is a smart strategy.
If only I could find a pattern.
Peter, it's time to march.
Go. March, march, march.
♪ Fish are small, bread is stale ♪
♪ Life is not a fairy tale ♪
- ♪ Life is not a fairy tale ♪
- Furry little paws.
Razor-sharp talons.
♪ ...fairy tale ♪
♪ Fish are small, bread is stale ♪
♪ Life is not a fairy tale ♪
♪ Fish are small, bread is stale... ♪
- Oh, what did you put in this?
- Turmeric.
Really? At dinner time?
I'm on it.
Excuse me? Peter?
Typically, we're spared marching
during the dinner hour.
Yes, sir.
I have to do extra because I spent
our dinner money on a Fortune Teller.
Mm. And what did they tell you?
To follow an elephant...
which doesn't exist.
Mm.
Yes.
But what if it did?
Leo Matienne!
My wife, she's tired of my "what ifs."
The elephant will lead me to my sister.
Peter! March, now!
A child shouldn't live like that,
marching and marching.
It's none of our business, Leo.
Now, at the exact same time across town,
there was a show with...
No, not that guy!
The opening act is a magician.
Thank you so much.
It's not going well.
Mystery and wonderment!
- Ace of diamonds!
- Nope.
The Hoops of Delirium!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh.
I have one final trick.
Excellent news!
I will need a volunteer.
Madam, if you please.
Please.
Have a seat, madam.
Can we just get it over with?
The Magician isn't great at magic,
but even if he was,
he realizes this crowd wouldn't care.
And that's what does it.
He decides to try a powerful spell,
something to restore
and revive all of Baltese.
One elegant,
invisible moment of profound change.
Now!
Like I said, he's not great at magic.
Let me explain!
Do you have a name?
What? What the...?
Hey! Hey, do you know what happened to
the Fortune Teller's tent that was there?
No tent there yesterday.
Mm. Was a tent once.
Maybe it was just laundry.
- Or a hat. I love hats.
- Great.
Does anyone know where the tent is?
The Fortune Teller!
- Have you seen a tent?
- ...an elephant.
An elephant? What? Wait, wait, wait!
Did you say elephant? Where is she?
They locked her up. And the Magician too.
It's just as she said.
Who did? What?
The elephant has come.
And what that means is my sister lives!
She lives! She lives, Mrs. Taylor!
Oh, lovely!
The elephant is here!
Ha!
An elephant?
The elephant is here!
- An elephant...
- An elephant!
- Yes, an elephant! An elephant!
I knew it would come!
- I knew it would come.
- You did?
No, but I had strong
and unreasonable hopes.
And sometimes that's enough.
She's locked up somewhere,
but I have to get her, sir.
I'll barter or sneak
or fight my way in somehow.
Yes. Yes.
But would you allow me to help?
But... how?
I'll speak to the Countess
and her advisers,
and you and I will...
We'll figure it out together.
Really?
Really.
Sergeant Lutz?
Sir!
Sergeant Lutz!
Elephants? Fairy tales? False hope!
No.
What?
No, sir. An elephant has arrived here!
- An elephant!
- An elephant will do you no good!
But it must be true, then!
My sister lives!
And I remember her.
Impossible! She died at birth.
No! I remember.
Sir,
have you ever lied to me?
What are you saying?
I'm saying she lives and I will find her.
Mm.
Yes.
Okay,
and... open!
Oh, what the...?
So, liberty!
That's unhelpful.
- You, sir! Why did you do this to me?
- Now, please...
- I didn't!
- Oh, you most certainly did!
- You brought me on stage!
- It was an accident.
Balderdash! You purposely
crushed my leg with an elephant!
No! It was... It was supposed to be...
Lilies. Yeah, that's it.
- A bouquet of lilies.
- Hey! What is all this?
No idea! It's outrageous!
Remove it at once.
Stand back, sorcerer!
I'm just an entertainer!
I am not entertained.
- They're only tricks.
- Assault.
How could I produce an elephant on purpose
when I can't even escape from a jail cell?
Look. Freedom!
Lima beans, my least favorite legume.
You're behind bars where you belong.
I'm going to make sure you stay there.
Chest up, shoulders back. Breathe.
Direct, but polite.
Strong, but respectful.
Sweaty and nauseous.
The Countess, she's fair and wise,
and no one can remember
the last time she laughed.
- She can sing!
- Can she sing?
Shh. Yes, Captain Matienne?
Thank you, Countess.
I've come to ask
where the elephant is kept.
Who sent you to ask?
Have you been approached
by a foreign power?
No. As captain of the palace guards,
I need to know.
The elephant is dangerous.
We don't even know where it came from.
The elephant is a criminal,
it is being treated as such.
A criminal? No.
- This may just be the opening barrage.
- Uh, what?
We must expect other beasts
to be launched at us!
Camels! Cassowaries! Crocodiles!
We commanded the Magician
to disappear her! He says he's unable!
As such, we plan to destroy her!
I haven't decided that.
If a boy throws a rock through a window,
can you blame the rock?
We're speaking of elephants.
- You're speaking of murder!
- The elephant committed a crime!
The elephant is guilty of nothing
except being an elephant!
I'll continue to consider this
until we meet tomorrow.
But let me say, Captain Matienne,
I take the safety
of our town very seriously.
She may need to be... gotten rid of.
- Hear.
- Agreed!
The only sensible solution.
Quite right.
Now,
Leo Matienne sees one other way
to keep the elephant alive.
The King.
Ah.
He knows two things...
- Mm. Huh?
- ...one, The King has never been to Baltese.
...over the palace wall,
landing safely in the moat.
That's impossible! I love it!
Two, The King likes to be entertained.
Only to be entertained...
...and never to not be entertained.
I love you, sir!
Hey, who wants a nougat? You like nougat?
And a doctor. And then they'll go again.
Fantastic stuff.
"An elephant came through a ceiling
and hit an old lady."
Are you kidding? Let's go!
The King!
His Majesty wants...
...to see the elephant!
- The... The King?
- Coming here?
- To see the elephant?
- Extraordinary!
- We must make preparations!
- Etcetera!
- Peter, what are you doing?
- Mr. Matienne?
I was going to come get you.
I said I'd help you see the elephant.
Oh, uh, I guess I just...
I... I'm just not used to that.
Help.
Come on.
Whoa.
Wow! You work here?
Mm-hmm.
- That's for the elephant?
- Mm.
Captain Matienne, is everything ready?
Yes, yes!
That's right! I'm The King!
Ooh!
Hey, everybody's here!
There's snacks!
Oh, this is the best, right?
I know! I know!
I wish I'd been there.
Oh!
Psst. Hey, it's her.
Hear, hear.
And now, the elephant.
Ha!
You're here!
- Wow!
- Ooh!
My word!
The sheer dimension of her!
Wow. Would you look at that.
I must admit,
she is a magnificent creature.
She certainly is.
She seems agitated.
Something's not right.
Her eye.
Can those chains hold her?
Protect them!
Shoot it! Shoot it!
No! No!
No!
Rifles down! Peter.
- Peter!
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
It's okay.
Come.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hey.
- You did it!
- Oh my God!
Young man.
Peter, ma'am.
Peter, I'm grateful.
I'd like you to stay at the palace
and tend to my elephant.
The elephant is staying here?
No, thank you, ma'am.
- Oh.
- The kid's got pluck. I love it!
I need the elephant to lead me
to my lost sister. It is my destiny.
"Destiny."
I must ask you to give her to me.
The elephant is very dangerous, Peter.
That's impossible.
I happen to like impossible things.
Hey, what if Peter
does three impossible things
in exchange for one?
We're here for three days.
Each day, I'll pick something
impossible for the kid to do,
and if he does all three, thus proving
his valor, strength, blah blah blah,
he gets the elephant.
If not, I'll take it back with me.
Well, I'm not sure...
It's a deal!
You're terrific, Countess.
I like this place more and more,
wherever we are.
Okay, the first impossible task is...
a fight!
- A fight?
- Sure!
Who doesn't like a fight?
And an impossible fight
is the best kind, right?
- Stands to reason, sir.
- The kid's up for it! I told you.
Right? He's got some idea
about the elephant.
- And destiny and...
- Uh...
I love it! Okay, tomorrow, noon,
the kid fights my toughest soldier.
Oh no.
- Pistols or sabers?
- Um...
Sabers it is! I love this kid!
Give him my saber, Henri.
It's all yours.
Unless you get killed, in which case,
you know, I'll take it back.
Peter, has any of your training
included sabers?
- No, sir. Broomsticks a bit.
- Mm...
Meet me at the store, if you like.
I'll try to teach you.
Tomorrow, at noon.
Coup d'arrêt!
Dérobement!
Yes!
En garde!
Lunge!
Mm-hmm.
Counter-parry!
Yes!
- I'm getting better.
- Absolutely.
Oh, madness. How can the boy win?
What if he does?
What if?
Your "what ifs" will be
the end of us, Leo Matienne.
I beg your pardon, ma'am. But how can
two small words be so dangerous?
In Leo Matienne's hands is how.
What if we put all our savings
into raising pygmy goats?
A perfect pet.
If they could've been trained
not to eat floors and walls.
What if we import rare goods
from the Far East?
Would've worked.
If the entire shipment
had not been eaten by pygmy goats.
They didn't eat the silks.
Ah-ha! Yes, the silk.
You see this roll of silk?
My husband wanted to use it
to kill himself.
It's called a parachute,
and there is evidence it can work.
- Has it ever worked?
- No.
Actually, the results have been
quite grisly. That's true.
But what if I had been the first?
I'm going to practice on the mannequins.
A good boy.
Whoa! Whoa!
Tireless and kind.
- Leo...
- But with no one to love him.
Don't say it.
And the two of us downstairs, all alone.
No, we've tried and failed.
God does not intend for us
to have children, Leo Matienne.
And who are we to say what God intends?
Please.
My heart has been broken too many times.
It cannot bear your foolish questions.
But how? How will the world ever change
if we do not question it?
The world cannot be changed.
The world is what the world is
and forever has been.
No.
I won't believe that.
For here is Peter, standing before us,
asking us to make it something different.
Lunge.
Coup d'arrêt.
Oh. Adele, my dear!
- Are you well?
- I dreamt of an elephant, Sister.
Oh, but how lovely.
I find elephant dreams
particularly moving and portentous,
although I'm forced to admit that
I myself have never dreamt of an elephant.
It felt like the elephant
came to take me somewhere.
Oh, but you belong right here,
dear child, where you're safe.
Hmm. Safe from what, Sister?
From the world.
I went out to see the world, Adele,
and it was cruel.
So I brought you home to the orphanage,
far away from everything.
And I named you Adele after your mother,
who's in heaven now with your brother.
Mm. Do you think elephants have names?
Oh, yes. All creatures have names, dear.
Every last one of them.
The elephant also has dreams.
The elephant's with her family...
and she hears her name spoken.
Somewhere she's known,
somewhere she's loved.
She definitely doesn't belong here.
It all seems impossible.
Hey.
It's all right, it's okay.
It's all right.
We met earlier, with the water.
Yeah, that was me.
You may not know it yet, but...
you've been brought here
to find my sister.
Uh, I don't know where she is.
To win you, I have to fight
The King's toughest soldier tomorrow.
But I thought instead,
all you have to do
is just point on this map
and show me where my sister is.
On... on the map.
Show me on this map here where she is.
Okay?
All right.
Just gotta point where...
Point where my sister is.
Are you a magic talking elephant?
Can you tell me where she is?
Can you speak? Just speak. Say it.
Say it.
Can you say it?
Hey!
Well...
Looks like I have to fight tomorrow.
So, I better keep practicing.
Thank you.
What's happening?
There's a boy fighting for the elephant.
It's time.
She lives.
Peter!
Peter, posta breve then moulinet!
Remember, with the spin!
And now, your opponent.
Oh no.
Oh, brilliant!
This is Sergeant De Smedt!
Huh? De Smedt?
A chase!
Even better!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh.
What do I do? Think!
De Smedt, have you got the boy?
De Smedt?
Romain De Smedt,
young soldier I served with.
I need his book!
Oh no!
Mm?
Psst!
I need the biggest fish you have, sir!
Peter?
- What are you doing...?
- Take this as payment.
Cod!
- Magnificent and versatile!
- Please!
Oh no!
- Thanks!
- Oh!
Yes!
Whoa!
I think I lost him.
I definitely haven't lost him!
Cod!
Magnificent and versatile.
Stiffen the wicks.
The situation has escalated.
There's a clear command structure.
I must find a way
to infiltrate their ranks.
There he is!
Sergeant De Smedt!
I'm here, Sergeant De Smedt!
De Smedt.
Sergeant De Smedt, I'm here!
What is this?
Oh!
Peter, you are a solider!
Remember our training!
The book! The book! Look!
The book! The book!
Huh?
My book.
One great whoosh of magic
freed the dragon from his evil spell,
and everyone lived happily ever after.
Well, that's all for tonight,
little carrot.
Mama, please? Just one more.
All right, carrot. Just a teeny.
What is going on there?
I've done some things.
In combat, I mean.
Do you believe a person can change?
I just beat you
in battle, Sergeant.
I think anything's possible.
Yeah, Peter!
Hooray!
Yay! Peter!
- Yeah!
- Yay!
I'm kind of amazed that worked.
Me too.
You've done the first impossible task.
You've also lost my priceless family saber
and ruined a perfectly good
killing machine.
"Hello," said Mr. Pig.
"Hello," said Mr. Rooster.
You're a surprisingly weird
and dangerous young man.
- And I like that.
- Thank you, sir.
Now, tomorrow,
for the second impossible task...
Uh...
Uh, you will fly!
- Huh? Fly? I... But...
- Fly?
- How?
- Hello? It's supposed to be impossible.
The kid just beat Goliath.
You want him to bob for apples?
Plus, we've had some people nearly fly.
What? I...
Right? Nearly.
Okay, great.
Tomorrow at noon,
we'll all meet in the square
and watch the kid fly or crash or both.
Both could be funny.
Like, like he really gets going
but then, whammo!
No, of course not. No. Um...
So, until then...
I will get you water,
and then I will learn how to fly
and then I will get you out of here.
And we can find my sister.
The elephant cannot
understand human speech,
but she can look at a face
and recognize friendship.
She doesn't feel well,
but she does finally
feel something like... hope.
And hope can spread
from one person to the next.
- He ran off like lightning!
- I know! I saw it with my own eyes.
He bestowed upon me this sword
in exchange for one cod.
I can't wait to see
what he has to do next.
I'm going early to get a good spot.
- He held up a book!
- Like an avenging librarian!
- Incredible! Who knows what's next?
- It could be anything.
An elephant!
♪ Bake me a cake as fast as... ♪
Sister! Sister! It's... an elephant!
In the hydrangeas?
In the city!
An elephant has appeared
under miraculous circumstances.
We must go!
No, no, no, no! We do not go to the city.
It is unsafe. Some harm could befall you.
But... my dream. This is a sign.
I do not believe in signs.
Yes, you do.
Yes.
I do, in fact, believe in signs.
Very well, dear.
Oh!
Perhaps you do not understand.
My legs were crushed!
By an elephant!
Yes, she comes here every day.
Every day.
Oh, look who's back.
Traitor.
- My legs were crushed!
- Go get help, boy.
By an elephant!
I know, your legs were crushed
by an elephant.
But for the last time,
I just intended a bouquet of lilies.
Just admit you crushed my legs
with your tricks.
It was an accident.
I intended a bouquet of lilies.
Lilies!
Stop all that! Just stop!
Peter...
Peter. Peter, just stop.
Stop this minute!
- Sir...
- Soldiers do not fly! I forbid it!
- Sir, I...
- No!
Now, you listen.
With De Smedt, you were lucky,
but this... this flying...
It is impossible.
I beat De Smedt, and I believe I will fly!
And I believe
you will be crushed flat. Dead.
Dead like your sister!
Huh? Oh...
Watch me!
Peter, what's wrong?
I have to fly tomorrow,
but I have no idea how to do that.
Vilna says that I'm going to die.
Like I don't know!
Like I don't already know.
I have to fly tomorrow. I have to.
Come inside. You need to eat.
And we'll talk.
Eat now.
What do you call this?
Stew, dear.
Okay, Peter,
now, about this flying business.
Please, stay close, dear.
Hello, honey.
As soon as you see the elephant,
we're going back to the orphanage
where we're safe.
- Help you with your luggage, Sister?
- Oh!
Quickly, dear. Quickly.
Now you see why
we don't travel to the city, Adele.
Danger at every turn.
Peter.
Peter, where are you?
Hello? Hello?
If only I'd kept the boy. The boy.
We're retreating to the garrison.
Oh.
Regroup at the garrison!
Go! Go! Go, go!
Run!
Retreat!
Fall back!
Hello? Hello?
Please, listen.
You have to get out of here.
We're retreating to the garrison.
Their mother, is she...?
Take the children. I'll meet you there.
I'm a soldier.
I don't know how to care for a newborn.
Of course. Just the boy, then.
Please, I can't do it alone.
All right. But you have to leave at once.
I'll gather things for the baby
and meet you at the garrison. Now, go!
I should have taken them both.
I'm so sorry, young man.
But I'll keep you safe.
I'm a soldier.
Peter.
Oh, the boy with me.
The garrison!
Is there anyone left?
No more survivors!
It's not safe here, Sister!
The enemy is coming!
If only I'd kept the boy with me.
- A new day.
- Hey, everybody! Hello!
A new impossible task.
And the same impossible King.
Great day to watch the kid fly, eh?
Not a cloud in the...
Oh, strike that.
It's a shame, really,
because, you know, with a tan...
...I become irresistible.
I'm still King, right?
I didn't miss a coup or something.
Does she ever laugh?
Never?
Like, not ever?
Not since her brother died in the war.
Oh dear.
Yeah!
They said the elephant would be here.
Can you see her, Sister?
Ooh!
Stay close, dear.
No, stay with me! Stay with me!
How's everybody doing?
Yes, it's me!
Okay. Let's see something impossible.
Uh, where's the kid?
Up there!
Well, that doesn't seem smart.
- He'll be all right.
- Uh-huh. Yes, sure.
Ooh.
No, no, no, no, no.
Whoa.
Whoa!
Ah!
Ahh!
No!
- What is it?
- The boy, he slipped.
No!
Hold on!
Phew.
Ugh!
Humph!
And now, I will fly!
He's gonna jump!
This was a fantastic idea!
I will find her.
Now, Peter!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Peter!
Wow.
I knew it!
I knew the kid could fly!
Yes!
Oh! It's possible!
You are flying, Peter!
You are flying!
What is possible?
It's possible! It's possible!
It's possible!  Peter!
He's flying!
Oh!
Whoa!
Peter!
Sorry! Excuse me!
Whoa!
Peter!
Amazing, Peter!
Whoa! Wonderful, Peter!
Ah!
Whoa!
Yay, Peter! Great job!
Peter! Peter! Peter!
Yeah!
- Yeah!
- Yes! Whoo!
All right, I flew! What's next?
Well, you've done
the second impossible task,
so, you are one step away
from owning an elephant!
It doesn't sound great when I say it
out loud. A lot of cleaning up.
Huge. Anyway. Okay. Good.
Okay, for the third impossible task...
Uh...
I don't have it yet.
No, I'm a spur-of-the-moment
kind of king, you know?
I... I come up with things
on the fly, you know?
Always winging it.
It's a joke. God, it's a quip, but...
Aha!
Nope. Nope. Sorry. Stand down, son.
I just get like this when I'm about
to say something incredible.
Okay, kid, you ready?
For your third impossible task...
you will make the Countess laugh.
What?
Oh.
They keep doing this.
What part of impossible
is tripping you people up?
Im, not. Poss, the middle part...
Im... Something...
Okay, I have no idea, but it means
"impossible!"
Plus, this kid's a killer.
Anyone thinks they're better
than this kid,
you're next jumping off
the cathedral wearing a tent.
Remember that.
You should stop worrying about the kid
and figure out who'll get me an ice cream.
Preferably butter pecan.
Anyone? Hello?
Why are we all standing here?
Oh! Adele!
Oh my goodness.
Hello.
It's me, from the dream. Do you remember?
I'm here. Can you tell me why?
This one may really be impossible.
I mean, she never laughs.
Not ever.
Maybe they'd let me
jump off the cathedral again.
I could write you a joke.
Sorry?
You're probably just not very funny.
Right, and I'm sure you're hilarious.
Ow!
Ow.
Very sorry, miss.
It's unlike me
to say something so insulting.
And I've never hit a person in my life.
Please forgive me.
- But I...
- Oh, there you are!
I was looking everywhere.
Are you all right?
Yes, Sister.
Well, now that you've seen the elephant...
Hello, madam.
Did she tell you anything?
No.
Very good, dear!
Now we can go home.
But, Sister...
We'll get a good night's sleep,
then go back to where we belong.
Hmm.
I get muddled sometimes, Peter,
little unclear about things.
I want you to know
I am perfectly clear
what I have to say right now.
You are right.
She was alive.
The little girl was alive.
I could have saved her.
I left her with the nurse.
We were supposed to meet at the garrison,
but there was an explosion.
I... I didn't think
I could tend to you both.
I'm a soldier, Peter.
What do I
know about an infant?
We make these decisions
in war, in life.
We have only a moment.
I could have saved you both.
I didn't.
And I lied
because I didn't want
to cause you any more pain.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Sir...
did you see her dead?
My sister?
No.
Then anything is possible.
Well...
you spoke of impossible elephants...
and were correct.
Sir?
You stood before an impossible opponent...
and you were victorious.
Then today...
...I saw you fly!
It's you, my boy.
You.
You are what is possible.
One more task tomorrow.
Well, then, tell me a joke.
A horse walked into a bar.
Um, maybe it can't walk into it.
No, no! That's not funny.
No.
Oh, yes.
Yes!
Yes, that is funny!
Madam LaVaughn,
I've lied to you.
Oh!
Finally, an admission.
No, I didn't mean to hurt you
or make an elephant appear,
but I wasn't trying
for a bouquet of lilies either.
Mm.
When I stood on that stage
facing all of you,
your disbelief...
...it... it made my heart break.
Even now, you see magic right before you,
things conjured from nothing.
Granted, a fractured magic,
sloppy, accidental, but...
magic.
To which you respond, "Stop,"
as you would to some minor nuisance.
What has happened here?
That night, I tried to cast a spell
on you and everyone else there.
A spell to make you believe again,
to care about magic,
because extraordinary things are possible.
If you believe!
But I had no business
attempting such a powerful spell,
because I'm not a very good magician.
I tried for mystery and wonderment.
It brought disaster.
I know.
I know you're worried
about the Countess laughing,
but I've got a great joke.
And I've got it under control.
You gotta trust me.
Hey!
I feel like you're not taking me
seriously. I'm a dangerous man.
I beat a giant, I jumped off a building.
Okay. okay. There'll be plenty of time
for messing about later.
We just have to concentrate
on the final task, but...
Oh, I can't wait to get you out of here.
We're gonna have so much fun
and so many adventures...
...finding my sister.
Hmm.
Wow!
Ya!
Woo-hoo!
Whoa!
Is this your family?
Peter!
Peter! Peter! Peter!
Peter.
Hey, wake up. It's time now.
Everyone's here, Peter. The third task.
Well, this should be interesting.
Oh!
You must really miss them. I thought
you were taking me back to my family.
I need to get you back to yours.
It's time for the third impossible task!
Will the kid finally win
the elephant?
Yes, I will.
Now, if at any point
I hear the Countess laugh,
you walk away with the elephant.
Proceed.
So, there's a farmer and a fisherman.
- They're out in a field together.
- Solid start. Classic.
When they hear
a funny kind of croaking noise,
they look over towards the pond
and they see a hen.
The hen's got this piece of string,
and she's working the string
in and out of the mouth
of a frog by the pond,
up and down with the string
in the frog's mouth.
So, the fisherman says,
"Why do you think the hen's doing that?"
The farmer turns
to the fisherman and says,
"Well, sure, it's the same question
as always, isn't it?"
Huh? Huh?
"Why did the chicken floss the toad?"
Nailed it!
Funny stuff, Peter! Funny stuff!
Oh, I get it.
Why did the chicken...?
Because it sounds like...
Hold on. Hold on.
That's not a real laugh.
If you're not gonna take this seriously,
Countess, then what's the point?
Sorry, kid, you failed.
Oh, Peter.
No.
What? No?
You have to let me take her,
but not for me, for her.
All this time, I've tried to win
the elephant to find my family,
but she has a family
and she was taken from them.
Peter, what about your sister?
The elephant might have a sister too.
Why is mine more important?
I know the joke didn't work,
but please, the elephant didn't ask
to be brought here.
We have to send her home.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Man, you almost had me.
But no.
You had one last thing to do,
and I don't see her laughing.
Grab the elephant and we'll roll.
No! No! No!
Okay, I know. This is impossible.
But what if it wasn't?
Just think for a moment.
Think of all
of the impossible things you've done,
and you've probably done plenty.
Have you ever gotten through
one of them alone?
Of course not. That would be absurd.
Peter fought and flew and defied a king,
and maybe he feels alone.
But he's not.
No one is. Remember that.
Let's go!
Oh no.
I...
All right, kid, you did it.
What? Really?
But... but it was the elephant.
She's laughing, right?
That's all I really wanted.
Things are only impossible
till they're not.
The elephant is yours, Peter.
What?
Glorious victory! Huzzah!
Yeah! Woo-hoo!
Yeah!
Wow.
We did it! We did it!
Mm. Whoa, whoa!
How will we get her home?
A barge across the sea!
A dirigible?
Carried over the mountains
by larger elephants!
That seemed good until I said it out loud.
The Magician!
Wake up now.
This boy says the elephant must go home.
You must make her disappear.
You've seen what happens
when I attempt that spell.
We're lucky it wasn't worse.
Sir, the elephant deserves
to be with her family.
Yeah, that's a lovely idea,
but look around you.
My magic is all failure!
- Failure?
- I can't do it!
Nonsense!
You brought an elephant through the roof.
And don't you realize
it started something here?
The very thing you wished for.
Hey, magic man!
Let's send the big lady home!
I believe that you can perform
the necessary magic.
I believe that only you
can set things right.
Sister! Sister!
Sister, please.
In my dream, I was meant to follow her.
I do not believe in dreams.
Yes, you do.
Yes, I do, in fact, believe in dreams.
Oh, very well.
Developments are afoot.
The battle must be joined.
Hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
I heard it was different here before.
There was light,
there was life, there was hope.
The perfect kind of town
to make an elephant disappear.
This is my home,
but it's not hers.
It's hard to lose a friend.
We have to say goodbye now.
The Magician brought her here,
and I believe that he can send her home!
Do you believe?
That is how it will be accomplished.
Please, sir.
Belief is a great and invisible thing.
It comes over us like sleep.
We struggle along the edges,
fighting it for reasons we cannot name...
until, as with sleep,
we lose ourselves.
We stop... and we are restored.
The elephant is gone!
I can't believe I just saw magic!
- What's happening?
- Look at the clouds!
It's magic.
It's clearing!
- What is it?
- It's sun, my darling.
It's good.
It's beautiful!
Sunshine!
You were meant to follow her
to your destiny.
This was more important.
Come on now, Adele. Time to go home.
Sir, you're outside!
Yes. Yes.
Oh.
The soldier?
You were dead.
Do you...?
Do you mean?
The boy!
Peter.
This is... this is my sister.
- You're...
- Well...
- First of all... Let me just say...
- You're alive! And here!
And family!
Come on, Peter!
Incredible!
Good stuff. Good stuff.
Oh.
Yeah!
He found her!
Ow! What was that for?
No more jumping off buildings!
The magic worked!
I'm sorry for the harm
I've caused you, madam.
I beg your forgiveness.
Oh, lilies!
Thank you, my friend.
Just look at the place now.
A town restored. Can you see?
You've been visiting
for a while.
I know, but every time I try to leave,
it just seems... impossible.
Just then, the magic coral woke up
and chased the oysters away shouting...
"Begone, evil mollusks!"
"Away!"
- Ooh, that was really scary.
- Thank you.
A whole family created.
How do you find exotic yarn?
Oh, I've got my secrets,
you know? I'm a big city lady.
Tell me you didn't make the goat
more pajamas. All he does is eat them.
Yes, but he likes eating pajamas.
Come on, while it's hot!
And as for the elephant,
she lives a really long time,
long enough to test
even an elephant's memory.
But of course, she never forgets Peter.
I mean, how could she?
♪ Any time you're feelin' low and lonely
Lost and broken ♪
♪ Even though you might not know
I'm always there ♪
♪ Always there ♪
♪ We all need to know
That someone sees us ♪
♪ We're all longing
For someone to reach us ♪
♪ And what you're
Looking, looking, looking for ♪
♪ Is here ♪
♪ So when you're out there
Feeling like there's missing pieces ♪
♪ Like there's something
You're still needing ♪
♪ Want you to know
If you feel lost, lost ♪
♪ Feeling all alone
That you're not alone now ♪
♪ Now doesn't it feel good
To be found, found? ♪
♪ Found, f-found, found,
Found, f-found, found, found ♪
♪ Now doesn't it feel good
To be found, found? ♪
♪ Found, f-found, found,
Found, f-found, found, found ♪
♪ Now doesn't it feel good? ♪
♪ Just to know that you can always know
That I got your back ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Just to know that through it all
I'm always there ♪
♪ Always there ♪
♪ So just know, just know
That someone sees you ♪
♪ Sees you ♪
♪ Who would walk across this Earth
To reach you ♪
♪ Reach you ♪
♪ Who will be there any, any time ♪
♪ Anywhere ♪
♪ So when you're out there
Feeling like there's missing pieces ♪
♪ Like there's something
You're still needing ♪
♪ Want you to know
If you feel lost, lost ♪
♪ Feeling all alone
That you're not alone now ♪
♪ Now doesn't it feel good
To be found, found? ♪
♪ Found, f-found, found,
Found, f-found, found, found ♪
♪ Now doesn't it feel good
To be found, found? ♪
♪ Found, f-found, found,
Found, f-found, found, found ♪
♪ Now doesn't it feel good
To find a friendly face? ♪
♪ In a world of strangers ♪
♪ You've felt so out of place ♪
♪ And now ♪
♪ Doesn't it feel good to be found? ♪
♪ Found ♪
♪ Now doesn't it feel good
To be found, found? ♪
♪ Found, f-found, found,
Found, f-found, found, found ♪
♪ Now doesn't it feel good? ♪
♪ When you're out there
Feeling like there's missing pieces ♪
♪ Like there's something
You're still needing ♪
♪ Want you to know
If you feel lost, lost ♪
♪ Feeling all alone
That you're not alone now ♪
♪ Now doesn't it feel good
To be found, found? ♪
♪ Found, f-found, found,
Found, f-found, found, found ♪
♪ Now doesn't it feel good
To be found, found? ♪
♪ Found, f-found, found,
Found, f-found, found, found ♪
♪ Now doesn't it feel good to be found? ♪